<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Game Of Thrones</string>
    <string name="Search">Search</string>
    <string name="searchResults">Search Results</string>
    <string name="infoString">Search fo characters by continent, gender and house. Choose zero, one, two, or three search criteria. To search by the character by name, click on the search method in the menu bar. Click on the results to learn more about the character.
    To start and pause the music, click on the music icon.
    To store a character into favorites, click the floating action button at the bottom of the screen. To leave a comment on the character, enter it into the edit text and press submit.</string>
    <string name="jonSnow">Jon is the bastard son of Lord Eddard Stark of Winterfell. He was a steward in the Night\'s Watch. Now serving on the Wall, Jon has found a place of acceptance where the circumstances of his birth are of little importance. He has a pet direwolf named Ghost, and wields the bastard sword, Longclaw, which was a gift from Lord Commander Jeor Mormont, who took Jon as his personal steward and came to see him as a surrogate son. Courageous and loyal to a fault. Leader of men. Great Fighter. He knows nothing.</string>
    <string name="aryaStark">Arya was born and raised at Winterfell. She has an older sister, Sansa Stark. She also has an older brother, Robb, two younger brothers, Bran and Rickon and a bastard half-brother, Jon Snow. \nArya rejects the notion that she must become a lady and marry for influence and power, feeling she can forge her own destiny. She is fascinated by warfare and training in the use of arms, and is bored by embroidery and other "lady-like" pursuits. She takes after her father and has a quarrelsome relationship with her sister Sansa, due to their contrasting interests and personalities. She is close to her half-brother Jon, who is also something of an outcast. Trained killer out for revenge. A girl must know her place.</string>
    <string name="danyTargaryen">Mother of Dragons. Daenerys is the only daughter and youngest child of King Aerys II Targaryen, the "Mad King", and his sister-wife Rhaella. Her father died during the Sack of King\'s Landing, before she was even born. The usurper Robert Baratheon installed himself as king, having defeated Aerys in the conquest known as Robert\'s Rebellion. Her pregnant mother and young brother Viserys, fled to the island of Dragonstone, the ancestral home of House Targaryen, to escape Robert. Daenerys\'s brother Rhaegar Targaryen was also killed in the war and Robert\'s forces murdered his wife and children, Daenerys\'s sister-in-law, niece, and nephew, during the Sack of King\'s Landing. \nOn the night Daenerys was born on Dragonstone, a vast storm raged. For this reason, she is sometimes called "Daenerys Stormborn". Her mother died soon after she was born, leaving her an orphan. As a baby, she was taken into exile in the Free Cities with her brother, Viserys, by loyal retainers, among them Ser Willem Darry. /nAfter years spent fruitlessly trying to raise support to retake the Iron Throne, Viserys and Daenerys were given sanctuary by Magister Illyrio Mopatis in the Free City of Pentos. She dreams of finding a peaceful home and a place to belong. She lives in constant fear of Viserys, who hits her when his temper is risen (in his words, whenever she "wakes the dragon"). Living under Viserys\' domination has left her meek and malleable.</string>
    <string name="jaimeLannister">Ser Jaime Lannister is a knight of the Kingsguard, the eldest son of Tywin Lannister, younger twin brother of Queen Cersei Lannister, and older brother of Tyrion Lannister. Previously he served in the Kingsguard of Aerys II Targaryen and, infamously, he betrayed and killed Aerys during the Sack of King\'s Landing, earning him the sobriquet "the Kingslayer". Jaime is involved in an incestuous sexual relationship with Cersei, and, unknown to most, is the biological father of her three children, Joffrey, Myrcella and Tommen. A true tale of redemption.</string>
    <string name="cerseiLannister">Cersei is the wife of King Robert Baratheon and Queen Regent of the Seven Kingdoms. She is the daughter of Lord Tywin Lannister, twin sister of Jaime Lannister and elder sister of Tyrion Lannister. She has an incestuous sexual relationship with Jaime, who is secretly the father of her three children, Joffrey, Myrcella and Tommen. She\'s loyal to her house and will do nothing to secure it\'s success. A real beezy. Shwerd and manipulative are her best qualities.</string>
    <string name="oberynMartell">Known as the Red Viper of Dorne, Oberyn is a member of House Martell, the ruling family of Dorne, and the younger brother of Doran Martell and the late Elia Martell, and the father of eight bastard girls known as the Sand Snakes. He is well known for his fighting skills, passionate temper, and sexual appetites. Best damn character on the show. Awesome with a spear. Wants to know who killed his sister. Not a fan of the Lannisters. Suffers from massive headaches. \nPrince Oberyn is the younger brother of Prince Doran Martell and Princess Elia Martell; like most members of House Martell, he is styled "Prince" instead of "Lord". He is nicknamed "the Red Viper" for his knowledge of poisons and for his unusual, deadly style of combat. Oberyn is known for being an accomplished warrior, but he is just as infamous for his sexual appetite, which extends to both men and women; Tyrion Lannister tells Bronn that Oberyn is "famous for fucking half of Westeros". Oberyn\'s paramour is Ellaria Sand; she is his wife in all but name, and Doran once noted that Ellaria made Oberyn very happy. She is also the mother of five of Oberyn\'s infamous eight bastard daughters, all of whom he has acknowledged and given his love and care. He named the fifth one, Elia Sand, after his late sister.</string>
    <string name="jofferyBaratheon">Though believed by most to be the eldest son of King Robert Baratheon with Queen Cersei Lannister, Joffrey is actually a bastard born from Cersei\'s incestuous relationship with her twin brother, Ser Jaime Lannister of the Kingsguard. He is the older brother of Myrcella Baratheon and Tommen Baratheon, both of whom share the same parentage. \nJoffrey takes after his mother in terms of looks and personality, his blonde hair being a subtle clue that he isn\'t really a Baratheon, who famously always possess black hair even when one of their parents possesses blonde hair. (Cersei herself lets it slip to Catelyn Stark that she once had a child with black hair who died prematurely before she had Joffrey.) He is usually accompanied by his sworn shield, the formidable Sandor Clegane, who is better known as the Hound. Even before he ascends to the Iron Throne, Joffrey is spoiled, arrogant, cowardly, and sadistic; however these traits are further exacerbated upon Robert\'s death and his ascension to the crown. \nKing of the Andals. Protector of the realms of man and a little bitch. Seriously may be the most disliked person in literary and television history.</string>
    <string name="robertBaratheon">Robert Baratheon was the ruler of the Seven Kingdoms, formally styled as Robert of the House Baratheon, the First of His Name, King of the Andals and the First Men, Lord of the Seven Kingdoms and Protector of the Realm. He took the throne through conquest in the war known as Robert\'s Rebellion. Robert was a great warrior in his youth. He killed Rhaegar Targaryen, Prince of Dragonstone, at the Battle of the Trident. After the war, Robert married Cersei Lannister to cement an alliance with House Lannister to hold the kingdoms together, but the marriage was loveless. Robert and Cersei have three children: Joffrey, Myrcella and Tommen. Unbeknown to Robert and most of the realm, however, all three were actually fathered by Cersei\'s twin brother, Jaime Lannister.</string>
    <string name="jorahMormont">Sir Friendzone. Ser Jorah is an exiled Northern lord living in Essos. He has sworn fealty to his fellow exile Daenerys Targaryen and helps her adapt to life as a Khaleesi of the Dothraki. Best voice in all the world. \nOriginally, Jorah was working as a spy for Varys, King Robert\'s spymaster in King\'s Landing, sending Varys information about the Targaryen exiles. But he grows to respect and admire Daenerys and begins serving her in earnest. He saves her from an assassination attempt, stops sending reports to Varys and ignores an official royal pardon which would allow him to return home to Westeros. He develops strong and unrequited feelings for her. When Daenerys learns of his past spying, he is dismissed from her service and ordered to leave her presence, but has recently given her the gift of Tyrion Lannister in a hope to earn her trust once more.</string>
    <string name="tyrionLannister">Tyrion Lannister is the youngest son of Joanna Lannister and Lord Tywin Lannister. Tywin is the head of House Lannister, the richest man in the Seven Kingdoms and Lord Paramount of the Westerlands. The Westerlands are one of the constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms and House Lannister of Casterly Rock is one of the Great Houses of the realm. He is the younger brother of Jaime and Cersei Lannister. His mother Joanna Lannister died giving birth to him. His father and sister hold him in contempt as they blame him for the death. \nHe is a dwarf, causing him problems and persecution. His size has led him to being referred to derisively by various names, such as "the Imp" and "The Halfman". This is mitigated by his intellect and his family\'s wealth and power. Had an infant with dwarfism like Tyrion been born a commoner, he\'d have simply been left out in the woods to die. However, Tyrion was born into a powerful noble House, and was therefore spared. Even though his father doesn\'t think much of him, he has had the benefits of being raised with wealth and education, and is expected to lead his life as a credit to the Lannister name. He is committed to the good of both his House and, since Cersei married King Robert Baratheon, his family\'s continued hold on the throne. \nIf he dies this show might as well end.</string>
    <string name="petyrBaelish">Petyr Baelish was the Master of Coin on the Small Council. He is a skilled manipulator and uses his ownership of brothels in King\'s Landing to both accrue intelligence on political rivals and acquire vast wealth. Baelish\'s spy network is eclipsed only by that of Varys. Kniving, and cunning. His motives are never known. Never to be trusted. Rose to power from nothing. He would watch the world burn if he could be king of the ashes.</string>
    <string name="varys">Varys is a eunuch and was the Master of Whisperers on the King\'s Small Council until he is forced to flee King\'s Landing with Tyrion Lannister. He is a skilled manipulator and commands a network of informants across two continents. Varys\' true loyalties are eventually revealed to be to Daenerys Targaryen (though she herself is initially unaware of this), as he believes her rule would be the best way to preserve peace and prosperity in the Seven Kingdoms. He and Tyrion travel to Meereen in the hopes of serving as her advisers. </string>
    <string name="jeorMormont">Jeor Mormont is the Lord Commander of the Night\'s Watch, and is the father of the exiled knight Jorah Mormont. He leads a great expedition ranging north of the Wall to investigate rumors of Free Folk amassing and White Walkers being sighted. He is killed at Craster\'s Keep by his own men after they rebel against the Lord Commander for not standing up to Craster.</string>
    <string name="doranMartell">Doran Martell is the Prince of Dorne and the Lord of Sunspear. He is the head of House Martell, the ruling house of Dorne, and the older brother of the late Princess Elia, who was murdered by Ser Gregor Clegane in the Sack of King\'s Landing, and Prince Oberyn. \nUnlike his more hotheaded and aggressive brother, Oberyn, Doran is a pensive, calculating, and patient man who always waits and observes before making his next move. Despite their different personalities, the two brothers were very close. While Oberyn could indulge in the wayward Dornish ways, challenging whomever he liked regardless of the consequences, Doran was raised to be more responsible as the heir to the Dornish throne. He truly cares for both his people and his family, and would never make a decision that would go against their interests. However, this is often against their wishes.</string>
    <string name="aegonTargaryen">King Aegon I Targaryen, known as Aegon the Conqueror, is an unseen character in Game of Thrones. He died almost three hundred years before the time of the series, and is not expected to appear. Aegon I Targaryen conquered all of Westeros (with the exception of Dorne) with three great dragons, Balerion, Vhagar and Meraxes, and unified the realm under his rule, founding the Targaryen dynasty. He was married to both of his sisters, Visenya and Rhaenys. He is a direct ancestor of Daenerys Targaryen.</string>
    <string name="eddardStark">Eddard is the head of House Stark, the Lord of Winterfell, Lord Paramount and Warden of the North, and Hand of the King to Robert I Baratheon. He is the older brother of Benjen Stark, father of Robb, Sansa, Arya, Bran and Rickon by his wife, Catelyn Tully, and to Jon Snow, his bastard son by an unknown mother. He is a dedicated husband and father, a loyal friend and an honorable lord. Winter is coming.</string>
    <string name="melissandre">She is a priestess of the Lord of Light and a close advisor to Stannis Baratheon in his campaign to take the Iron Throne, but ultimately abandons him after her actions inadvertently lead to the destruction of his family and army and flees to Castle Black. \nOriginally born a slave in Essos, Melisandre is a Red Priestess of the Lord of Light, a deity that is not widely worshiped in Westeros. Hailing from Asshai, a country located in the far east of the continent of Essos, she claims to wield powerful magical abilities, particularly the power of prophecy. Melisandre wears a large ruby necklace that seems to glow whenever she performs her magic. Some years ago she crossed the Narrow Sea and came to the court of Lord Stannis Baratheon on the island stronghold of Dragonstone, to preach her faith. Stannis and the majority of his household have now converted to her religion, and she has become a close adviser to Stannis himself.</string>
    <string name="branStark">Crippled who can see visions. Son of Eddard Stark. Hopefully his role get more interesting.</string>
    <string name="tywinLannister">Tywin Lannister was the head of House Lannister, Lord of Casterly Rock, Warden of the West, Lord Paramount of the Westerlands, Hand of the King on three occasions, and Protector of the Realm. He is the father of Cersei, Jaime and Tyrion Lannister, and grandfather of Joffrey, Myrcella and Tommen Baratheon.</string>
    <string name="viserysTargaryen">Viserys is the second son and heir of King Aerys II Targaryen, the former ruler of the Seven Kingdoms. During Robert\'s Rebellion, after Viserys\'s older brother Rhaegar was killed at the Battle of the Trident, his father sent Viserys and his pregnant mother Queen Rhaella to safety on Dragonstone island. King Aerys was soon afterwards killed during the Sack of King\'s Landing along with Rhaegar\'s widow and children, and thus at the age of only five Viserys became the titular head of House Targaryen, though by this point the war was officially lost.[1] Not long afterwards, his mother died in childbirth, while the forces of Robert Baratheon closed in on the island. Before they could arrive, Viserys and his baby sister Daenerys were smuggled to safety in the Free Cities, across the Narrow Sea on the continent of Essos. Bereft of followers, Viserys spent the next 17 years travelling between the Free Cities trying to find new supporters for an attempt to retake the Iron Throne. At times, however, he was left literally begging for food and shelter, much less an army. He\'s a large douche.</string>
    <string name="jaqenHghar">"Jaqen H\'ghar" is just an assumed identity of one of the Faceless Men of Braavos, a feared order of mysterious assassins with the ability to change their appearance at will. After the Jaqen persona is of no more use to him, the Faceless Man shapeshifts into a new appearance and tells Arya he will train her to be a Faceless Man if she goes with him. Eventually, Arya travels to Braavos to look for Jaqen and finds him, and he trains her.</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search for character</string>
    <string name="margaery">Margaery is the widow of King Renly Baratheon, a claimant to the Iron Throne in the War of the Five Kings. Her father Lord Mace Tyrell is the ruler of the Reach. She is betrothed to King Joffrey Baratheon after the Battle of Blackwater, and briefly becomes his queen, but this is cut short when Joffrey is fatally poisoned at their wedding feast. She subsequently was betrothed to Joffrey\'s younger brother and successor, Tommen Baratheon. Margaery is known for her beauty, political cunning, and ambition, although she has a compassionate side. Due to Cersei Lannister\'s machinations, Margaery has recently been arrested by the Faith Militant for perjury on her brother Loras\'s behalf, and the two are to stand trial.</string>
    <string name="loras">Ser Loras Tyrell, the heir to Highgarden, is a popular tourney knight and ranks as one of the most skilled knights in Westeros. He was the lover of Renly Baratheon and supported his claim to the Iron Throne as commander of his Kingsguard. After Renly is murdered, Loras correctly deduces his brother Stannis Baratheon is responsible and swears vengeance. He joins forces with King Joffrey and Tywin Lannister in the War of the Five Kings, and helps them defeat Stannis at the Battle of the Blackwater. Since then, however, he has been arrested by the re-established Faith Militant for his homosexuality, and is set to stand trial.</string>
    <string name="stannis">Younger brother to Robert. Father of the year candidate. Entitled to the throne in his opinion. Believer in the Lord of Light.</string>
    <string name="sansa">Sansa was born and raised at Winterfell. She has an older brother, Robb, two younger brothers, Bran and Rickon, a younger sister, Arya and a bastard half-brother, Jon Snow. Sansa enjoys proper "lady-like" pursuits, and is good at sewing, embroidering, poetry, singing, dancing, literature and music. She dreams of being a regal Queen like Cersei Lannister, and that just like in the epic songs she will meet her knight in shining armor. She has inherited her mother\'s Tully coloring, unlike most of her siblings, and Lady Catelyn thinks Sansa will be even more beautiful than she was when she was younger. She is often seen in contrast with her sister, Arya Stark who has neither her looks nor her accomplishments in feminine activities and comportment. One of the most unfortunate characters in the books or show. Her storyline just gets worse and worse. It says something that she downgraded from Joffery.</string>
    <string name="ramsay"> Ramsay is the bastard son of Lord Roose Bolton, recently legitimized by the crown, thus making Ramsay Roose\'s lawful heir to Winterfell and the North. \nThe scariest character in the world quite possibly. He will torture you in the worst possible ways and laugh as he does it. Seriously that sausage scene.</string>
    <string name="roose">Roose Bolton is the head of House Bolton, a vassal family to House Stark of Winterfell. He is the Lord of the Dreadfort. Roose takes pride in his house sigil; the flayed man. Although torture is outlawed in the North, his family is famous for flaying the skin from their enemies as a means of torture and execution. Roose fought for Lord Eddard Stark in the civil war against House Targaryen known as Robert\'s Rebellion and proved his worth as a soldier in the Battle of the Trident. He advised Robert Baratheon to execute Ser Barristan Selmy, a legendary Kingsguard sworn to the Targaryens, but Robert overruled Roose and pardoned Selmy. He will send your regards.</string>
    <string name="davos">The Onion Pirate. Raised up to a Lord by Stannis Baratheon. A man that will fight for what he believes in. Truly underrated character. \nDavos is one of Stannis\' most loyal and reliable vassals and arguably his best friend, but is treated with disdain by some of the other lords of Westeros for his low birth. Stannis himself points out that it was the low-born Davos, and not the high-born lords, who saved the lives of Stannis and his castle garrison. Davos is one of the only men who can (even grudgingly) influence Stannis\' decisions, because he values Davos\' honest advice above that of noble-born flatterers.[</string>
    <string name="robb">King of the North! Eldest son of Eddard Stark. Events thrust him into a leadership position. Great general. Married for Love, which is dumb.</string>
    <string name="bronn">The coolest sellsword in Westeros. While Bronn begins as a common and obscure mercenary, over the course of the narrative his fortunes continue to gradually rise. Bronn is briefly appointed Commander of the City Watch in King\'s Landing when Tyrion is acting Hand. He is then rewarded with a knighthood for the vital role he performed during the Battle of the Blackwater, taking on the formal name "Ser Bronn of the Blackwater". His status in Westerosi society rises even further when he is betrothed to Lollys Stokeworth, though the betrothal is annulled and he is sent to Dorne with Jaime Lannister to rescue Myrcella Baratheon from the vengeful family of Oberyn Martell. He is poisoned by Tyene Sand and almost dies, but survives and is allowed to leave Dorne.</string>
    <string name="brienne">Lady Brienne is not much a lady. One of the greatest fighters in Westeros but never gets her credit. Her Valyrian Steel blade is name Oathkeeper.</string>
    <string name="hodor">Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor</string>
    <string name="khal">My moon and stars. Drogo is a khal or warlord of the Dothraki, the famed nomadic horse-lords of the eastern continent beyond the Narrow Sea. The Dothraki are fierce warriors, skilled in battle, unrelenting in combat and known for savagery towards non-Dothraki. Amongst their own people they have a code of honor, albeit still a harsh and unforgiving one. Drogo was very young to have his own khalasar, particularly such a large one. He is a legendary warrior and has never been defeated in battle. Drogo desired the most beautiful and exotic woman in the world as his khaleesi or wife, and enlisted Magister Illyrio Mopatis of Pentos to help him find such a woman. Only two dudes in the world can rock I makeup. He\'s on of them.</string>
    <string name="olenna">The Queen of Thorns. The elderly matriarch of House Tyrell, Lady Olenna has been a master of court politics and intrigue par excellence throughout her life. She\'s also known for her wit and sarcasm. As a result, Lady Olenna is popularly nicknamed the Queen of Thorns, in reference to her House\'s sigil and her cutting barbs. In many ways she is the de facto head of House Tyrell at the time of the War of the Five Kings and appears to hold a great deal of influence over the Reach.</string>
    <string name="tommen">Younger brother to Joffery. Nothing like his brother. A kind, warm hearted boy. However I really don\'t care anything about him.</string>
    <string-array name="continent">
        <item>No Selection</item>
        <item>Westeros</item>
        <item>Essos</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sex">
        <item>No Selection</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="house">
        <item>No Selection</item>
        <item>Targaryen</item>
        <item>Stark</item>
        <item>Martell</item>
        <item>Mormont</item>
        <item>Baratheon</item>
        <item>Lannister</item>
        <item>Tyrell</item>
        <item>Bolton</item>
        <item>None</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
