<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Game Of Thrones</string>
    <string name="Search">Search</string>
    <string name="searchResults">Search Results</string>
    <string name="infoString">Search fo characters by continent, gender and house. Choose zero, one, two, or three search criteria. To search by the character by name, click on the search method in the menu bar. Click on the results to learn more about the character.
    To start and pause the music, click on the music icon.
    To store a character into favorites, click the floating action button at the bottom of the screen. To leave a comment on the character, enter it into the edit text and press submit.</string>
    <string name="jonSnow">Jon is the bastard son of Lord Eddard Stark of Winterfell. He was a steward in the Night's Watch. Now serving on the Wall, Jon has found a place of acceptance where the circumstances of his birth are of little importance. He has a pet direwolf named Ghost, and wields the bastard sword, Longclaw, which was a gift from Lord Commander Jeor Mormont, who took Jon as his personal steward and came to see him as a surrogate son. Courageous and loyal to a fault. Leader of men. Great Fighter. He knows nothing.</string>
    <string name="aryaStark">Arya was born and raised at Winterfell. She has an older sister, Sansa Stark. She also has an older brother, Robb, two younger brothers, Bran and Rickon and a bastard half-brother, Jon Snow. \nArya rejects the notion that she must become a lady and marry for influence and power, feeling she can forge her own destiny. She is fascinated by warfare and training in the use of arms, and is bored by embroidery and other "lady-like" pursuits. She takes after her father and has a quarrelsome relationship with her sister Sansa, due to their contrasting interests and personalities. She is close to her half-brother Jon, who is also something of an outcast. Trained killer out for revenge. A girl must know her place.</string>
    <string name="danyTargaryen">Mother of Dragons. Daenerys is the only daughter and youngest child of King Aerys II Targaryen, the "Mad King", and his sister-wife Rhaella. Her father died during the Sack of King\'s Landing, before she was even born. The usurper Robert Baratheon installed himself as king, having defeated Aerys in the conquest known as Robert\'s Rebellion. Her pregnant mother and young brother Viserys, fled to the island of Dragonstone, the ancestral home of House Targaryen, to escape Robert. Daenerys\'s brother Rhaegar Targaryen was also killed in the war and Robert\'s forces murdered his wife and children, Daenerys\'s sister-in-law, niece, and nephew, during the Sack of King\'s Landing. \nOn the night Daenerys was born on Dragonstone, a vast storm raged. For this reason, she is sometimes called "Daenerys Stormborn". Her mother died soon after she was born, leaving her an orphan. As a baby, she was taken into exile in the Free Cities with her brother, Viserys, by loyal retainers, among them Ser Willem Darry. /nAfter years spent fruitlessly trying to raise support to retake the Iron Throne, Viserys and Daenerys were given sanctuary by Magister Illyrio Mopatis in the Free City of Pentos. She dreams of finding a peaceful home and a place to belong. She lives in constant fear of Viserys, who hits her when his temper is risen (in his words, whenever she "wakes the dragon"). Living under Viserys\' domination has left her meek and malleable.</string>
    <string name="jaimeLannister">Ser Jaime Lannister is a knight of the Kingsguard, the eldest son of Tywin Lannister, younger twin brother of Queen Cersei Lannister, and older brother of Tyrion Lannister. Previously he served in the Kingsguard of Aerys II Targaryen and, infamously, he betrayed and killed Aerys during the Sack of King\'s Landing, earning him the sobriquet "the Kingslayer". Jaime is involved in an incestuous sexual relationship with Cersei, and, unknown to most, is the biological father of her three children, Joffrey, Myrcella and Tommen. A true tale of redemption.</string>
    <string name="cerseiLannister">Cersei is the wife of King Robert Baratheon and Queen Regent of the Seven Kingdoms. She is the daughter of Lord Tywin Lannister, twin sister of Jaime Lannister and elder sister of Tyrion Lannister. She has an incestuous sexual relationship with Jaime, who is secretly the father of her three children, Joffrey, Myrcella and Tommen. She\'s loyal to her house and will do nothing to secure it\'s success. A real beezy. Shwerd and manipulative are her best qualities.</string>
    <string name="oberynMartell">The VIPER!! Best damn character on the show. Awesome with a spear. Wants to know who killed his sister. Not a fan of the Lannisters. Suffers from massive headaches.</string>
    <string name="jofferyBaratheon">King of the Andals. Protector of the realms of man and a little bitch. Seriously may be the most disliked person in literary and television history.</string>
    <string name="robertBaratheon">Rose up in rebellion and secured the iron throne. Husband to Cersei. A drunk and an all around great ruler.</string>
    <string name="jorahMormont">Sir Friendzone. Loyal to Daenerys Targaryen and banned from the seven kingdoms. Best voice in all the world.</string>
    <string name="tyrionLannister">Also known as the Imp and the Halfman. Cunning and wise. The only Lannister worth a damn kinda. I do enjoy Jaime now. Don\'t let his height full you. If he dies this show might as well end.</string>
    <string name="petyrBaelish">Also known as Littlefinger. Kniving, and cunning. His motives are never known. Never to be trusted. Rose to power from nothing. He would watch the world burn if he could be king of the ashes.</string>
    <string name="varys">Sneaky unich from essos. Master of whispers, he knows all that happens in the kingdom. His allegiances are to Westeros. His little birds are everywhere.</string>
    <string name="jeorMormont">Commander of the Night\'s Watch. Father to Jorah. Gave Jon Snow his Valyrian Steel blade.</string>
    <string name="doranMartell">Lord of Dorne. A cripple. A man with a plan to be revealed soon.</string>
    <string name="aegonTargaryen">Aegon the Conqueror. First of his name. Conquered the seven kingdoms with his dragons. Last of the great Valyrian Empire. He created the kingdom of Westeros we know today.</string>
    <string name="eddardStark">Goes by Ned. Loyal man, Warden of the North, and Lord of Winterfell. Robert Baratheon\'s righthand man in his rebellion. Winter is coming.</string>
    <string name="melissandre">The Red Woman. Priestess for the Lord of Light. Believees Stannis Baratheon is the reincarnated Azor Ahai.</string>
    <string name="branStark">Crippled who can see visions. Son of Eddard Stark. Hopefully his role get more interesting.</string>
    <string name="tywinLannister">Warden of the East and Lord of Casterly Rock. One of the richest and most powerful lords in all the kingdoms. Not a man to be messed with.</string>
    <string name="viserysTargaryen">Viserys is the second son and heir of King Aerys II Targaryen, the former ruler of the Seven Kingdoms. During Robert\'s Rebellion, after Viserys\'s older brother Rhaegar was killed at the Battle of the Trident, his father sent Viserys and his pregnant mother Queen Rhaella to safety on Dragonstone island. King Aerys was soon afterwards killed during the Sack of King\'s Landing along with Rhaegar\'s widow and children, and thus at the age of only five Viserys became the titular head of House Targaryen, though by this point the war was officially lost.[1] Not long afterwards, his mother died in childbirth, while the forces of Robert Baratheon closed in on the island. Before they could arrive, Viserys and his baby sister Daenerys were smuggled to safety in the Free Cities, across the Narrow Sea on the continent of Essos. Bereft of followers, Viserys spent the next 17 years travelling between the Free Cities trying to find new supporters for an attempt to retake the Iron Throne. At times, however, he was left literally begging for food and shelter, much less an army. He\'s a large douche.</string>
    <string name="jaqenHghar">Assasain with many faces. Helps Arya in to train to be an assasain for the Many Faced God.</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search for character</string>
    <string name="margaery">Desperately wants to queen. She will marry anyone in order to secure that. Well versed in the Game of Thrones.</string>
    <string name="loras">Member of the Kingsguard, a gifted knight and jouster. He likes dudes.</string>
    <string name="stannis">Younger brother to Robert. Father of the year candidate. Entitled to the throne in his opinion. Believer in the Lord of Light.</string>
    <string name="sansa">Eldest daughter of Eddard Stark. One of the most unfortunate characters in the books or show. Her storyline just gets worse and worse. It says something that she downgraded from Joffery.</string>
    <string name="ramsay">The scariest character in the world quite possibly. He will torture you in the worst possible ways and laugh as he does it. Seriously that sausage scene.</string>
    <string name="roose">Lord of the dreadfort, sigil is the flayed man. Quiet and meticulous. His motives are to secure more power to House Bolton. He will send your regards.</string>
    <string name="davos">The Onion Pirate. Raised up to a Lord by Stannis Baratheon. A man that will fight for what he believes in. Truly underrated character.</string>
    <string name="robb">King of the North! Eldest son of Eddard Stark. Events thrust him into a leadership position. Great general. Married for Love, which is dumb.</string>
    <string name="bronn">The coolest sellsword in Westeros. He\'s a skilled fighter and is loyal to whichever Lannister will pay him the most.</string>
    <string name="brienne">Lady Brienne is not much a lady. One of the greatest fighters in Westeros but never gets her credit. Her Valyrian Steel blade is name Oathkeeper.</string>
    <string name="hodor">Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor Hodor</string>
    <string name="khal">My moon and stars. This dude is awesome. Khal to one of the largest khalsars in all the world. Feared fighter. Married Daenerys. Only two dudes in the world can rock I makeup. He\'s on of them.</string>
    <string name="olenna">The Queen of Thorns. Her name is apt. She is the true power in Highgarden. She always find a way to get things done that benefit her family.</string>
    <string name="tommen">Younger brother to Joffery. Nothing like his brother. A kind, warm hearted boy. However I really don\'t care anything about him.</string>
    <string-array name="continent">
        <item>No Selection</item>
        <item>Westeros</item>
        <item>Essos</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sex">
        <item>No Selection</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="house">
        <item>No Selection</item>
        <item>Targaryen</item>
        <item>Stark</item>
        <item>Martell</item>
        <item>Mormont</item>
        <item>Baratheon</item>
        <item>Lannister</item>
        <item>Tyrell</item>
        <item>Bolton</item>
        <item>None</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
